This woman has come
to The Synagogue, Church of All Nations
with the problem of difficulty
in walking due to rheumatoid arthritis
and she's using a wheelchair for the past 7 years.
You can see the bandage tied around her
knees which she uses to reduce the pain
she encounters on a daily basis.
This is the wheelchair she uses every day
to move from one place to another
because she cannot walk with her legs.
Her family members demonstrate the difficult task of carrying her into the wheelchair
in order to move her around.
Jesus Christ healed and still heals all manner of sicknesses and diseases.
Never a sickness, He cannot heal.
Never a disease, He cannot cure.
Never a healer like Jesus Christ.
My name is Diane Ebele Okeke.
I am from Abuja.
I'm 30 years old.
I cannot walk due to rheumatoid arthritis,
which has affected all of my body
and I am now confined to a wheelchair.
I have been having this sickness - rheumatoid arthritis - for the past seven years.
I have been confined to a wheelchair for the past four years because I cannot walk.
I have tried all solutions to no avail.
I have gone to different hospitals, prayer houses, churches, herbalists
but there was no solution.
It has affected me to the extent that I cannot do my house chores.
I have a small baby. I am supposed to nurse my baby ordinarily
but it is my husband who is helping me to bathe her
and my sister helps me to feed and take care of her.
I can't do anything on my own. I can't bathe. I can't even feed.
I am a graduate and this problem started after my youth service.
Since that time, I'm not happy
because I can't do anything on my own.
I can't even finish my career.
It started when I was 23 years old - seven years ago. Now, I am 30.
For the past seven years, I have been at a standstill.
Nothing - I can't do anything.
I'm not happy because when I see my age mates and see where they have reached,
I feel so sad.
She has come to The Synagogue, Church of All Nations
with the belief in her heart that with just a touch from Jesus Christ
through the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
she will get made holy in Jesus' name.
Her sister demonstrates how she pushes her from one place to another in the wheelchair
due to this problem of rheumatoid arthritis.
I believe that by stepping into this place, the arena of liberty,
she will be healed. She will not go back the same.
HEALING TIME
You're my last hope, Man of God! I am dying!
For the past seven years, I cannot walk. I have been using a wheelchair for the past four years.
I'm from Abuja. Man of God, help me! I'm dying!
I'm too young for this sickness. Man of God, I can't carry my baby.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer
At The SCOAN Saturday Prayer Line In Jesus' Name
Healing in Jesus' Name
Healed in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, I can walk!
Healed in Jesus' Name
My sister can walk now.
For the past four years, she had been on a wheelchair.
Thank You, Jesus! She can walk now!
Thank You, Jesus!
My name is Diane Ebele Okeke.
I'm from Abuja.
I could not walk due to rheutmatoid arthritis for the past seven years.
I had been to different places - hospitals, native doctors, different churches
but I could not get a solution until I came to The SCOAN.
I could not hold anything with my hands or carry my baby.
I could not to my house chores. My husband had been doing everything for me.
I could not cook, wash clothes or eat because it affected my gums and teeth.
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me today!
I came all the way from Abuja with my sister to The SCOAN.
I had been using the wheelchair for the past four years.
My sister introduced me to Emmanuel TV and I have been watching it.
She told me that we should come to The SCOAN because it was Prophet T.B. Joshua's birthday.
I had the opportunity to be registered and right now, I can walk.
I could move, after the man of God touched me.
I am healed; thank You, Jesus!
Thank You for healing me today!
Thank You for using the man of God, T.B. Joshua, to wipe away my tears of seven years.
Thank You, Jesus!
For the past four years, I had been on a wheelchair.
I could not move or do anything.
After my service, this problem of rheumatoid arthritis started, seven years ago.
I started having pain all over my body and joints.
I could not move my hands or fingers.
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me!
Thank You, Jesus! My sister has been healed!
My name is Madu Veronica.
She is healed now and she can walk.
She had not been walking for four years.
This sickness had been holding her down for the past seven years.
She could not do anything in the house except with the help of her husband.
Sometimes, when I visited her, I would help out.
She has a small baby in Abuja that she could not do anything for.
She could not even breastfeed her.
We came all the way from Abuja and thank God we came to the arena of liberty
and she is healed by the prophet of our time.
She is healed, in the name of Jesus.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Diane Ebele Okeke.
I come from Abuja (Nigeria).
What brought me to The SCOAN was the problem of rheumatoid arthritis,
which affected my whole body - my joints, neck, legs and knees.
I could not walk for the past seven years
and I was confined to a wheelchair for four years.
I had been to different hospitals from 2009, when I finished my NYSC
but there was no solution.
They gave me all kinds of medications and the pain became worse.
This affected me that I could not conceive anymore.
All the drugs they gave me did not work; they caused me stomach pain.
They told me that I would not be able to conceive again.
I had been praying to God to show me the solution.
I had been to different hospitals but there was no solution.
The pain affected me so much that I could not do my house chores or carry my baby;
even when I gave birth to my baby, it was by the grace of God that I managed to give birth to her.
After delivering her, I could not breastfeed or carry her.
My husband helped me to do all the house chores with my sister beside me.
I could not dress myself or cook; I could not do anything by myself.
Then, I decided to go to church.
I went to different churches and prayer houses, all to no avail - no solution.
My sister called me to say that I should go to The SCOAN, the arena of liberty,
to finally get my solution.
We came to The SCOAN from Abuja and the man of God prayed for me.
Immediately the man of God prayed for me, I felt an electric shock
and all my whole body began to vibrate.
I didn't know what was happening
until he said, "Stand up and walk!"
I stood up and started walking.
I don't know how to thank God.
Come on - you can do better than that! Put your hands together!
Hallelujah!
Mrs Diane Ebele Okeke - Healing Testimony
What a God of miracles!
Tell your neighbour: What a God of miracles!
As a young lady, for the past seven years, since I was 23, I had not been happy.
But today, I thank God that I can do what I could not do before.
I am so happy that I can use both of my hands to dress myself again.
I can eat, unlike before when it affected my teeth and jaw.
I am so happy that I am healed.
Amen. Well, indeed, we want to rejoice with you. Can you walk to the glory of God,
in the midst of the children of God?
Hallelujah! Let's clap for Jesus!
Mrs Diane Ebele Okeke - Healing Testimony
That is the very lady who received her healing in the name of Jesus Christ!
Walking freely to the glory of God!
My name is Madu Veronica.
The lady beside me is my sister.
The man at the other side is our uncle.
The problem started seven years ago.
She called me on the phone and said that both knees were hurting her.
It thought it was a normal pain until, as time went on, the pain got worse.
It affected all her joints and her whole body.
She could not do anything by herself, except with the help of her husband, house help
or me, whenever I had the chance.
It affected her so seriously that she could not even bathe herself.
I knew that immediately she would step on this land, she would not go back the same.
Mrs Madu Veronica (Diane's Sister) - Healing Testimony
We had gone to various churches, hospitals and herbalists but no solution was found.
In fact, people of God, I used to watch these things on Emmanuel TV.
This is our first time of coming here.
Yesterday, I was right behind her, looking at her.
The man of God prayed for her and touched her.
The next thing I saw was that she started vibrating.
I was so joyous and happy.
I want to tell you that yesterday, when we got home, she started sleeping.
She slept like a baby from 7pm, when we got to our hotel, till 9am.
This is something she could not do before.
This morning, I was expecting her to call me
but I had told myself that if she called me to help her put on her clothes, I would not.
Fortunately, she did not call me because she dressed herself. I thank God!
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Testimony Time
Madam, what can you say concerning this miracle?
How can you describe the miracle that took place in the life of your sister?
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I told my sister, "Let's go to the arena of liberty".
I want to tell you that Prophet T.B. Joshua is the prophet of our time.
With what I saw yesterday, I am so happy.
It's real; it's not magic, it's not rocket science - it happened live.
You experienced it live and direct.
It happened in the life of your family; indeed, it happened in the life of your sister
and you witnessed first-hand that Jesus Christ is real.
He is the same yesterday, today and forever.
Right now, we want to hear from your sister once more.
How is your body now? Are you still experiencing those pains that you had before?
No, I'm free; I can do what I could not do before.
I can raise my leg, I can shake my body and neck; I can do everything I could not do before.
Oh, hallelujah! Clap for Jesus!
Testimony Time
Indeed, whom the Son of God sets free is free indeed!
I want to advise the whole world, especially young people,
suffering with this kind of pain or sickness that has confined them to a wheelchair.
They should be patient and wait for God's time.
I never knew I would walk again as medical people had told me I would not walk again.
I want to advise them to be patient and trust in God.
One day, He will surely answer them.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Indeed, God is with us. Let's clap for Jesus!
Wonderful advice: Be patient and wait for God's time.
Once again, we rejoice with you, madam, for the wonderful healing
that has taken place in your life
and we know that as you continue to make the Word of God the standard for your life,
that this healing will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.